Johnny Vargas

Orem, Utah, United States



17vargajoha@washk12.org



linkedin.com/in/johnny-vargas-8081531b7

Summary

Hello! My name is Johnathan Vargas.

I have 3 years of experience working in the IT field. I have experience managing servers, hundreds of users, and any sort of hardware imaginable. I am proficient in system administration, server maintenance, hardware support, and software support. I also have 3 years of experience in coding classes. I am proficient in data structures and algorithms, python, web development, and regular expressions.

I also code some side projects in my free time just for fun, so head over to my github profile if you'd like:

https://github.com/johnnyvargas17

Experience



Information Technology Specialist

Mountainland Technical College

Oct 2020 - Present (11 months +)

Information technology specialist at Mountain Land Technical College.

Managing servers, computers, and user accounts. Troubleshooting software and hardware issues across all campuses.

IT Support Specialist

Mozenda

Jan 2019 - Sep 2020 (1 year 9 months)

Managing clients, and writing custom regular expressions and javascript to get client's data needs. Over these two years I have managed dozens of service projects, scraping millions of lines of data. I would perform data analysis as well on all of these projects.

Learned project managing experience, client success experience, how to write HTML/Javascript, and how to write Regular Expressions. I great combination of client/people skills and technical skills.

Customer Service Representative

Response Marketing

Aug 2018 - May 2019 (10 months)

Taking inbound and outbound calls from customers regarding marketing services. Learned great customer service experience, and also learned sales skills via selling over the phone.

Garden Center Associate

Walmart

May 2017 - Aug 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Learned great customer service skills, learned how to work hard and for long hours. Learned how to man the cashier, and stock shelves. Great job experience.

Education



Utah Valley University

Computer Science, Computer Science 2017 - 2022

Skills

Engineering • Project Management • English • Communication • Strategy • Data Analysis • Python (Programming Language) • Regular Expressions • XPath • JavaScript